{
    "id": "6468b81413784966a6e427677ca59bfd",
    "title": "Direct And Indirect Speech Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The stranger asked Harry if ........................... a clever boy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was he",
                "he was",
                "he is"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "09dcd9e7d66c4924a3e16a1efb70c918"
        },
        {
            "question": "The little girl asked me if I .................... in God.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "believe",
                "did believe",
                "believed"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "301d175fc42a412c881953c565cd29b8"
        },
        {
            "question": "The teacher asked the boy if he ................... the answer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "knows",
                "does know",
                "knew"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "54fcdddec4804eec9b00cabcc589cfe4"
        },
        {
            "question": "The man asked the boy if he .................. there yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "went",
                "had gone",
                "has gone"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "4db240edc1d44844b5ba2e179b6de60c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Mr. Smith asked me if I ....................... to a zoo.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "ever go",
                "ever went",
                "had ever been"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "dc7c2d58d1c242ccba28b8cb6f04ace4"
        },
        {
            "question": "The old woman asked me if I ......................any difficulty in finding her address.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did have",
                "have",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c6fa2a2d3010464d8d540151a18d2e67"
        },
        {
            "question": "I asked the boy if his father .................... to work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did go",
                "went",
                "had gone"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "44b3b42513534f509aa303057a1c5bff"
        },
        {
            "question": "The girl asked if she ..................... go home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "may",
                "might",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a855e6c2888c41849995ed15b779cdb6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Mark asked if they ........................ invite John to the party.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "can"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "175ecbf018284dfe9908d7c3ed92d72f"
        },
        {
            "question": "John asked Peter if he ................... his new car.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has seen",
                "saw",
                "had seen"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "bfa339dd41d24779b0db0d6db7515448"
        }
    ]
}